Guide to the Ann Brewer Knox papers, 1935-2011 MS2305
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Personal and professional papers, circa 1935 to 2011; 1977-2011; Series 2
  - Journals, 1976-2011; Series 2 Subseries 1
    - Journals, 2009 May 22 - 2010 Feburary 24; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Journals, 2010 January 9 - 2010 October 31; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Journals, 2010 May 4 - 2011 March 21; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Journals, 2010 December 8 - 2011 March 31; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Journals, 2011 March 28 - 2011 May 10; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Journal / notebook, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Journal, undated; Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Biographical and publishing material, circa 1935 to 2011; 1977-2011; Series 2 Subseries 2
    This subseries contains childhood poems, material related to schools and colleges she attended, photos, resumes, publication material, public relations material, clippings, grant applications, mailing lists, and poetry by other authors. This material documents the personal and professional writing and teaching career of Ann B. Knox, excluding most of her poetry and short story writings. The bulk of the material dates from 1977 to 2011, when Knox was active in this work. Some earlier material dates from her childhood, including adolescent poems, and school and college material dating from circa 1935 to 1980.
    Arranged into groups of like materials with personal material placed before professional material.
    - A.B.K. early / juvenelia poems, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Early writings college, circa 1945-1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - A.B.K writings, circa 1945-1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - MA catholic university thesis, 1969; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Thesis ms, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Thesis ms, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Checkhov paper, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Ray carver goddard college, circa 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Goddard admissions & money, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Goddard general info, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Goddard reports, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Misc poems from goddard classes, circa 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Goddard supplementary course material, circa 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Bibliographies on writing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - W.W. handouts, 1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Goddard annotated bibliography, 1978-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Goddard evaluation, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Goddard women wilson addresses, 1979-1981; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Ann b. knox transcripts and references, 1946-1976; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - PR photos, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Reumes, circa 1984-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Reumes and bios, circa 1995-2000; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Chronology, circa 1998; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Lists, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Fiction sent out, 1998-2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Poetry circulation current, circa 1992-2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - List of publications, circa 1984; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Fiction in print, 1995-2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Poems in print, 2009-2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Acknowlegments poems in print, 2009-2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Poetry acceptances, 1977-2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Acceptances fiction, 1979-2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Poetry acceptances, 1997-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Poetry rejections, 1977-2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Fiction rejections, 1984-2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Fiction ms rejections, 2006-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Ms rejections, 2007-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Poetry rejections, 2002-2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Readings, 1985-1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Readings, 1985-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Reading Rennaisance project, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Readings, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Readings - notes, circa 2008-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Readings, 2010-2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Last reading, 2011 May 10; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Clippings, 1987-1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Clippings and PR, 1987-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - PR and clips, 1988-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Clips and PR, 1988-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Late summer breaks (l.s.b.) PR, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - P.m. l.s.b. reviews, PR, 1995-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - L.s.b. reviews, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Interviews l.s.b. clips, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - L.s.b. publicity/clips, 1994-195; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - L.s.b. PR material, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Paper mache and l.s.b. PR, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Paper mache readers group questions, circa 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Paper mache, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Paper mache, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Paper mache, 1994-1999; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Paper mache author questionaire, circa 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Staying in nowhere, circa 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Staying in nowhere cover possibilities, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Staying pr, circa 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Bookstores (p.m.), 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - WWPH, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - WWPH, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - WWPH production guidelines, 1986-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - WWPH anthology bids, 1992-1995; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - WWPH kweli smith audio tapes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Scop laurels, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Poetry presses, 2002-2005; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - L of C anthology, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Old age - L of C, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Dark edge publishers, circa 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - The dark edge, 2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Finishing line press, 2006-2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Finishing line press, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Free lunch publication, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Notes in notebook, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Notes misc., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Notes / journal, 1992-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Poetry business call for poems, 201-2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Current biz, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Poetry biz, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Editing lit mag, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Submissions, 2008-2011; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Professional organization, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Essay about ann knox and writing, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Kumin "laurels" interview, circa 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Amy clampitt includes interview, 1991-1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Amy clampitt interview, 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Interviews, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Interview - bache, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Bibliographies on writing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Articles, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Articles on writing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Articles on writing, circa 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Booh logs - ready (w. copies), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Odds and ends poems, circa 2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Theodore roosevelt pageant, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Zen seminar, circa 2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Western trip, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Misc. essay, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Misc. comments on writing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Misc. material, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Judy po' others, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Wayeresbae-wareis studies, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Poems brother, 2010; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Friend's work, 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Poems friends etc, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Assorted poems by assorted poets, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Poems by other writers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Effie kimball, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - John Burghardt, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - John Burghardt, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 25)
    - S. dobyns metaphor, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Poems by various writers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Rona chang photos, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Friends, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Old friends, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Penna arts co. grant requests, 1986-1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Pa council on arts grant, 1990-1992; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Pa arts council grant, 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Pa grant application copy, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Pa council on the arts application, 2000-2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Pa council on arts poetry, 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - NEA grant application, 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - NEA, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Mailing lists, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Mailing lists, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - P.m. mailing lists, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Handwritten notecards [1/3], Undated; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Handwritten notecards [2/3], Undated; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Handwritten notecards [3/3], Undated; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Handwritten notecards [1/3], Undated; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Handwritten notecards [2/3], Undated; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Handwritten notecards [3/3], Undated; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Bibliography Notecards, 1981; Series 2 subseries 2 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1977-2011; Series 2 Subseries 3
    Arranged alphabetically by last names.
    This subseries contains letters, postcards, cards, e-mail, and other correspondence. Some of material is personal in nature and some of the material relates to her writings. The common names in the correspondence include Rona Chang, Joan Daw, Barbara Greensburg, David Huddle, Ann Leventhal, Heather McHugh, Warren Miller, Sidney Mitchell, Steven Tapscott, and Hilary Than, and the correspondence dates from 1977 to 2011. Some correspondence is also located in other subseries folders, especially correspondence related to drafts and publishing material.
    - Cathy breeden, 2005-2006; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Rona chang, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Rona chang, 2010-2011; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Barbara Davis, circa 1968-2010; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Joan daw, 1980-1993; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Joan daw, 2002-2003; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Joan daw, 2007-2009; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Barbara greensburg - goddard college, 1979; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Hadas - crit and correspondence, circa 1995; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - David huddle, 1980-1981; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Ann leventhal, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Heather mchugh, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Warren miller, 1981-1989; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Sidney mitchell, 1983-1988; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Steve tapscott, circa 1978; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Hilary tham, 2001-2002; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Letter from writers, 1993-1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Letter to ABK from writers/students [1 of 2], 1977-2002; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Letter to ABK from writers/students [2 of 2], 1983-1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Letters literary, 1997-1999; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Reading the tao e-mails, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Pats on the back, 2005-2009; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Other, 1992-2011; Series 2 Subseries 3 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Writing groups, workshops, and teaching material, 1984-2011; Series 2 Subseries 4
    Arranged into groups of like materials: writing groups, conferences, and teaching material.
    This subseries contains teaching material, poetry by other authors, and papers related to writing groups and workshops. This material documents the personal and professional writing and teaching career of Ann B. Knox, excluding most of her poetry and short story writings. The material dates from 1984 to 2011, when Knox was active in teaching and participating in workshops.
    - Hill group ABK poems, 2003-2011; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Hill group my poems, 2009-2011; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Hill group poems theirs, 2009-2010; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Hill group poems theirs, 2009-2010; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Hill group poems theirs, 2008-2011; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Hill group theirs, 2011; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Hill group others, 2007-2008; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Hill poetry group others, 2002-2006; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Hill poetry group others, 2004-2008; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Hill group others, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Antioch, 1986-1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Antioch writers conference, 1987; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Antioch, 1987-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Antioch writers conference, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Antioch, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Antioch, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Antioch writers conference, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 1991-1992; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 1995; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 2007; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Atlantic center for the arts, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Atlantic center for the arts handouts, 2008; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Plum writers retreat grennan workshop, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Plum workshop, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Plum, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Plum, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Virginia center for the creative arts residency, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Virginia center for the creative arts, 1992-1993; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Virginia center for the creative arts, 1994-1995; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Virginia center for the creative arts, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Virginia center for the creative arts, 2003-2004; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Aspen writers conference, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Collington poety group, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Ucross, 1996-1997; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Writers day, 1990-1997; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Writers day, 1997; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Writers day, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Writers day, 2001; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Treaching - ex - hjc writers day, 1995-1996; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Frost place festival, 2010; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Wesleyan conference, 1984; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Frostburg writing conference, 1986-1994; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Workshop ellen bass, 2009; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Creative writing festival for senior adults, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Teaching workshop nat'l, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - WC classes, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Poetry class, 1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Poetry class, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Poetry class, 2003; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Class notes, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Class, 2002; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - S.S. opeing class, 1998-1999; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Beginnings t, 1989-1994; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Writers on writing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Scene (t), circa 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Sending out, 1998; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - T. revision / craft, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - T. revision, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Teaching photos, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - POV, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Plot / story, 1989; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Opening class, 1988-1991; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - T. journal examples, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Teaching letters, circa 1997; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - S.S. exercises, 1998-2002; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Elements of story, 1989-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Dialogue, 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Character, 1988-1990; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Crits s.s., 2002; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - T. books about writing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Teaching xerox of beginning paragraphs etc., undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Stories misc. xeroxed, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Teaching poetry, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - T. poetry samples, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - Teaching poetry handout poems, 2000; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Books about poetry, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Poets on poetry, 2007-2009; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Poems by misc. writers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Masks, undated; Series 2 Subseries 4 (Box 69, Folder 26)